<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<message>
  <content></content>
  <embed colour="15434884">
    <title>Welcome to the CompSoc server!</title>
    <content><![CDATA[
CompSoc is the University of Edinburgh's society for anyone interested in tech.

════════
    ]]></content>
    <field>
      <title>SUMMARY OF CHANNELS</title>
      <content><![CDATA[
We have channels for general and academic chatting, each CompSoc interest group, The Tardis Project, and more.

Most of them are more-or-less obvious from their names, but here is a brief introduction for you:

- <#315277951597936640> is for any and all chat
- <#426505712697344003> if you don't want to shitpost in #general
- <#776739926536355852> for job postings, career chat, advice
- <#697038282701406298> for elections, politics, news, and stuff that might burn you out
- <#715859587148021850>, <#315278744572919809>, <#315278752508805131>, <#315278779054292992>, <#315278821362368512>, <#409847179247747073> for relevant academic chat. If you're on the MSc, pick inf5!
- <#359905927643791360>, <#730146239315837052>, <#900328057708089385>, <#408325783988469760>, <#315506334864769024>, <#761642631259750411>, <#761638659476029447> for relevant [Special Interest Groups](https://comp-soc.com/special-interest-groups)
- <#315278844842213379> for The Tardis Project

━━
      ]]></content>
    </field>
    <field>
      <title>WHAT ARE ALL THE BOTS?</title>
      <content><![CDATA[
CompSoc bridges communication between multiple platforms to allow you to chat across technical borders! At the moment we have Discord and IRC — so people on IRC show up as bots on Discord! Don't worry, we're not under a massive bot attack or anything :)

━━
      ]]></content>
    </field>
    <field>
      <title>WANT TO HELP SHAPE COMPSOC?</title>
      <content><![CDATA[
If you are a first year, you can apply to become a first-year representative in autumn of your first year! This is a common and easy way to familiarise yourself with internals of the CompSoc org!
For all other positions (including President, Secretary, Treasurer), elections for the subsequent academic year take place at the **Annual General Meeting** in April! You can nominate yourself!

━━
      ]]></content>
    </field>
    <field>
      <title>INVITES</title>
      <content><![CDATA[
If you want to invite your friends to this server, send them this:
[`https://comp-soc.com/chat`](https://comp-soc.com/chat)
If you know they prefer Discord you can use this invite link:
[`https://discord.com/invite/e4y8Vy5`](https://discord.com/invite/e4y8Vy5)
      ]]></content>
    </field>
  </embed>
</message>
